Hello,
hello friends, welcome to AppStock friends,
ICICI Bank's quarterly results have arrived.
First of all, you should see here. The
company has announced a split by sharing it at ₹5. From
now on, after getting this approval, the split will be
distributed. Okay, now we'll
move on to the company's quarterly results.
Here is the result. First of all, you should see the
numbers in crores.
Now I'll adjust it a little bit
in the skin so that it's easier to see.
This is this year's number, this previous Biryani
Water Three's number, and this last year's
Quarter Four number is given here.
We'll start here with the total income,
which this time is 27,408.12. Last year's
figure was 27,000.69, and last year's figure
was 23,000.953. So you can say that the
results are showing very good growth,
and quarterly
growth is also very good.
In the company's total, this is about income, which is very
good, but expenses are
also very important to look at.  It is important to look here. The
company's total expenditure, i.e., expenses, is
written, but the promise has not yet been added to it.
This time,
ICICI Bank's total expense is
17,119, which was 16,921 in the previous quarter
and 15,000,413 in the previous year
's quarter. This year, the
company's expenses are slightly higher than last year, and a
slight increase is being seen in this quarter compared to the previous quarter. This is
normal, there is no
problem. The company's
operating profit is written here, but it is
not the company's net profit. There will be a
process in this, then tax will also be done,
after that, the company will have the
net profit of the company.
Look, process is written here. Let me
explain a little about the problem here.
Actually, what is the business of the bank?
Taking loans and giving money. Now, the money which is not recovered,
which does not come back, means that the
bank considers that money to be
bad luck. Only such money is
put in the process category. There is a promise, take it there.  This is
a kind of loss. Now
how will it be adjusted? It is pocket adjusted,
meaning the profit is removed from the proper use.
Therefore, the lower the promise,
the better it is. Look here, the
providential figure is given. It
was 1068 in the previous quarter of 2007 and
2883 in the quarter for the previous year.
Compared to both last year and the previous quarter, this
time the provision has been reduced significantly, so you
can say because this figure will
act as a leading point for ICICI Bank. Now
look here, the net profit is written, that is,
what is left in the hands of the company after providing for providential and tax - that is
7018. I will rotate it a bit so that
you understand clearly. Look, this is 7018, the
net profit of ICICI Bank this time,
which was 6,193 in the previous quarter
and 4402 in the previous quarter.
Compared to last year, the company's
profit is on the verge of doubling this year. And
compared to the previous quarter, the
company's profit has increased very well in this quarter as well.
Well, good.  The thing is that ICICI Bank's
profit has been very good. Now let's take a
look at the GPS here, I will
adjust it a little in speed.
Look here, it is written that this time it is
10.10 and in the previous quarter it was
0.93 and in the quarter for last year it was
6.37. Compared to both last year and the previous quarter, there is a huge
increase in IPS this time. It is a good
thing that the profit of the company has improved, so
this will also be better. Now let's take a
look at one more important thing here, which is
NPA, which is very important data. This
MP means non-performing asset, such money
which is not sunk but is also not being recovered
and it has been more than 90 days. The
bank puts such money in the back alley,
that is why the more it is profited,
the better it is.
Look here, Gross NPA is written, which
this time is 33901.19 and in the previous quarter it
was 37,000.52 and last year's quarter
formula was 41 thousand.  373 I am saying honestly that this
time the result of ICICI Bank has been very good
or the result has been quite good here
and the quarter end
quarter also seems to be decreasing here
now see here the baby is given then it is
also given in the message form here,
you can see it if you want, so friends
according to me I have already told you that
this time the quarter for career of ICICI Bank has been
really very good, if you
have this share then you can buy it without any hesitation, so that's all the
information for now, if you liked it then do like this video
and if you are new to the channel
then keep subscribing to this channel
because we keep bringing updates related to the share market on
this channel, so we will
meet in the next video, till then
goodbye